holymoly.com 2011-01-02

# Privacy Policy | Holy Moly!

**HOLY MOLY PRIVACY POLICY**

_Holy Moly Entertainment Limited (referred to in these terms and conditions as " **Holy Moly** ", " **we** ", " **us** " or " **our** ") is committed to protecting your privacy on-line. We use the information we collect about you to provide services to you when you visit our website currently located at _[_www.holymoly.co.uk_](http://www.holymoly.co.uk/) _(the " **Site** "). At Holy Moly, we appreciate that you do not want any personal information you provide to us distributed indiscriminately and here, we explain how we collect information, what we do with it and what controls you have._  
__   
_It is your responsibility to read and understand this Privacy Policy. If you do not understand or accept this Privacy Policy then you should call our Customer Services team whose contact details are set out below. If you do not agree to all of this Privacy Policy and do not wish to be bound by it, you are not authorised to access or otherwise use the Site._

__   
**What data do we collect?**  
****  ****  
So that we can provide a personalised service, we may, upon registration or at other times, ask you to submit personal information such as a name, e-mail address, postal address and telephone number. You may also be able to order products, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters or participate in one of our online forums or communities. The types of information that may be collected at these pages include: your name, e-mail address, postal address, and telephone/mobile number, your gender and date of birth.

  We may ask you for other information, including, but not limited to, your interests, opinions and the way you use the Holy Moly service to assist us in our initiatives outlined above and to improve our understanding of customer trends and patterns.

  You are under no obligation to provide such information. However, if you should choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with certain services.

  **How is the information used?**  
****   
Holy Moly will use the information you provide to us to:

\- monitor, develop and improve the Site, services and your experience;

  \- assist in and administer the provision of services to you (i.e. dispatch news and Holy Moly communications via email, post, fax or phone);

  \- process and deal with any complaints or enquiries made by or about you;

  \- investigate any suspected breach of our Terms and Conditions use or the breach of other terms and conditions otherwise relating to you and to monitor compliance including by way of checking postings or submissions to the Site, retaining forum or chat room exchanges and using keyword triggers to investigate usage that may be inappropriate; and/or

  \- understand customer trends and patterns.

Where and only where requested by you we will:

  \- send you and keep you updated with information by email, telephone (including SMS) or mail about existing and new services and special offers from us; and/or

  \- send you information by email, telephone or mail about related products or services of selected third parties that may be of interest to you. However, you always have the opportunity to remove your consent to such use by sending an email to [ [customerservices@performgroup.com](mailto:customerservices@performgroup.com) ] with your request;

  \- We may on occasion combine information we receive online with other records to enhance our ability to notify you of our products and services that we think will be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive these notifications please send an e-mail to [ [customerservices@performgroup.com](mailto:customerservices@performgroup.com) ] letting us know.

You can tell us not to contact you or share the information with a third party either at initial registration or later through updates or amendments to your personal information. We may occasionally contact you about products and services we feel may be of interest to you. This will only come from us (or our agents) and only if you have indicated that you do not object to these offers.

  **With whom is the information shared?**  
****   
At times, Holy Moly may enter into co-branding arrangements with other reputable organisations, with whom your personal information may be shared. You can, however, tell us not to do so at any time, by sending an e-mail message to [ [customerservices@performgroup.com](mailto:customerservices@performgroup.com) ] letting us know.

  Holy Moly may disclose your personal information to business partners or sponsors, but this is specifically described to you prior to collecting the data or prior to transferring it.

  Holy Moly may disclose aggregate statistics about our site visitors, clients and sales in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers and other reputable third parties and for other lawful purposes, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.

Holy Moly may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or if it believes that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights, property or personal safety of Holy Moly, the site or its visitors.

  The Site contains links to other sites. Holy Moly is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of such sites.

  **Security**  
****   
Holy Moly places a great importance on the security of all personally identifiable information associated with visitors to the Site. We have security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of visitor data under our control. For example, our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorised personnel have access to user information. While we cannot ensure or guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur, we use our best efforts to prevent this.

  **Use of cookies**  
****   
Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your hard drive to store and sometimes track information about you. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can change your browser to prevent that. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of a website if you do so. Cookies are specific to the server that created them and cannot be accessed by other servers, which means they cannot be used to track your movements around the web. Although they do identify a user's computer, cookies do not personally identify users and passwords and credit card information are not stored in cookies.

We may use cookies to:

  - identify who you are and to access your account information;

  - estimate our audience size and patterns;

  - control how often visitors see similar ads; and

  - track preferences and to improve and update our Site.

For more information on cookies and how to disable them you can consult the information provided by the Interactive Advertising Bureau UK at <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>

  **Limitation of Liability**  
****   
The Site may contain links to other sites where information practices may be different to ours. For example, if you "click" on a link, the "click" may take you off the Site. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we are not responsible for and have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

  We sometimes may offer content (e.g., competitions, sweepstakes, or promotions) sponsored by or co branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that you voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. We are not responsible for and have no control over these third parties' use of this information. However, we will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such information.

  We may use a reputable third party to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at the Site. This Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that a third-party ad server may have collected from you.

**Where is the information stored?**  
****   
Information which you submit via the Site is sent to a computer located in the United Kingdom. Information submitted by you may be transferred by us to our other offices and to other reputable third party organisations, which may be situated outside the European Economic Area.

  In addition if you use our services while you are outside the EEA, your information may be transferred outside the EEA in order to provide you with those services.

  **Keeping our records accurate**  
****   
We aim to keep our information about you as accurate as possible, but we depend on our users to update their personal information whenever necessary. You can review, change or delete the details you have supplied to us at any time by clicking on this link [insert e-mail or my/account/details link]. If you have another query relating to your information, please contact us as set out below.

  **Legal Disclaimer**

We are not responsible nor will be liable to you in any way for events beyond our direct control. Because of the complex and constantly changing nature of our technology and business, we cannot guarantee nor do we represent that our Holy Molyance will be error free, and to the maximum extent permitted by law we will not be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, consequential or punitive damages or other loss suffered by you and relating to the use or release of your personal information.

  **Protection of Children**  
****   
The Site is not intended for or directed to persons under the age of 18. Any person who provides their personal information to us through any part of the Site must be 18 years of age or older. If we become aware that any person below this age has attempted to or has submitted personal information via the service, we will not accept their personal information and will take steps to remove such personal information from our records. This may involve us having to access and verify the age and other relevant details of such person.

  **Your acceptance of these terms**  
****   
By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Holy Moly and to this Privacy Policy.

  **Updates**

****   
We reserve the right, from time to time, and at our sole discretion, to change or update this Privacy Policy.

  All changes to this Privacy Policy will be published on this page and on the Site. Upon publication, each change will become effective and you will be deemed to be aware of and bound by it. You should therefore review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure that you are up-to-date with the current terms of the Privacy Policy.

  **Contact Us**  
****   
Please e-mail any questions, concerns or comments you have about this Privacy Policy to [ [customerservices@performgroup.com](mailto:customerservices@performgroup.com) ] or write to us at:  
Holy Moly Entertainment LimitedSussex HousePlane Tree CrescentFelthamTW13 7HE

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 30 September 2008.
